{"data":[{"question":"One of the essential features of the modern skyscraper is being the elevator.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"essential ","b":"modern skyscraper","c":"is being ","d":"elevator","answer":"3","explain":"- Is being-> is","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"A rabbit moves about by hopping on its hind legs, which are much longer and more strong than its  front legs.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"moves about ","b":"by hopping ","c":"which are ","d":"more strong ","answer":"4","explain":"- More strong-> stronger","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The snowy egret is about the size of large crow. \n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"snowy","b":"about","c":"the size","d":"of large crow","answer":"4","explain":"- Large crow-> a large crow","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"During the Middle Ages, handwriting notices kept groups of nobles informed of important events.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"During ","b":"handwriting","c":"kept ","d":"informed of ","answer":"1","explain":"- During-> in","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Tenant farmers are those they either rent a farm and work it for themselves or work the farm for the owner and receive payment.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"they ","b":"work it ","c":"or ","d":"the owner ","answer":"1","explain":"- They-> who","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Slightly over half of the population of El Paso, Texas, says both English and spanish.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Slightly ","b":"half ","c":"population ","d":"says ","answer":"4","explain":"- Says-> speaks","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Not since Gerald Reed has a chief executive served two full terms or leave Washington with cheers ringing in his ears.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"medium to large ","b":"common ","c":"in eastern ","d":"central areas ","answer":"3","explain":"- In eastern->in the eastern","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Artist Helen Frankenthaler returned home from college on 1949 to her native New York, the city producing the most art revolutionary of the day.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Approximately ","b":"all persons ","c":"were enrolled ","d":"course","answer":"4","explain":"- Course-> courses","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The doctor's records must be kept thorough and neatly, so as to insure good book-keeping.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Natural ","b":"primarily ","c":"animals ","d":"vegetable ","answer":"3","explain":"- Animals-> animal","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The Suwannee River has been never important for transport and no significant hydropower potential.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"As ","b":"melts","c":"dirt ","d":"deposit","answer":"4","explain":"- Deposit-> deposits","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"}]}